Guide to the Stanford University, Provost's Office, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Office of Management and Budget, Series 4
  - 04-560 Mitchell Building Earth Sciences, 1979- (Box 43, Folder 31)
  - 04-560 Mitchell Building Mechanical Systems, 1979- (Box 43, Folder 32)
  - 04-650 Roble Gym, 1979 (Box 43, Folder 33)
  - 04-700 Terman Engineering Library, 1979 (Box 43, Folder 34)
  - 04-700 Terman Engineering Library, 1978- (Box 43, Folder 35)
  - 04-700 Samuel Morris Way, 1977- (Box 43, Folder 36)
  - 05- General, 1979- (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - 05- Center on Student Residences Energy Consultant, 1979- (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - 05-10 Lagunita Court, 1979- (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - 05-100 Roble Hall, 1979- (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - 05-200 Florence Moore Hall, 1979- (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - 05-300 Knoll, 1979- (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - 05-350 Boathouse and Lake, 1979- (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - 05-350 Boathouse and Lake 1974 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - 05-350 Boathouse and Lake 1966-73 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - 05-450 Kappa Sigma House--535 Campus, 1979- (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - 05-510 Lake House, 1978- (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - 05-520 Lambsa Nu--658 Lomita Court, 1979- (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - 05-530 Kappa Alpha House--664 Lomita Court, 1979- (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - 05-540 Alpha Delta Phi--375 Campus, 1975- (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - 05-600/610/620 Robert S. Moore House, 1977- (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - 05-600/610/620 Robert S. Moore 1975 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - 05-800 Golf Driving Range, 1979- (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - 05-900T/910T Music Modular Building, 1979- (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - 05-900T/910T Music Modular Building, 1977- (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - 06-40 Encina Commons, 1979- (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - 06-50 Eating Clubs, 1979- (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - 06-100 Branner Hall, 1979- (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - 06-200 Toyon Hall, 1979- (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - 06-400 Wilbur Hall, 1979- (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - 06-500 Stern Hall, 1979- (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - 06-600/650 Manzanita Park and Laundry Building, 1979- (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - 06/910T/920T Office of Development, 1979- (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - 07-? Nuclear Magnetic Resonance Center 12-84 - 4-85 (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - 07-? Nuclear Magnetic Resonance Program Statement 10-83 (Box 44, Folder 29)
  - 07-? Nuclear Magnetic Resonance 12-82 - 12-83 (Box 44, Folder 30)
  - 07-? Nuclear Magnetic Resonance 11-83 (Box 44, Folder 31)
  - 07-? Nuclear Magnetic Resonance 2-84 (Box 44, Folder 32)
  - 07- Governor's Lane, 1978- (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - 07- Medical Center, Animal Facilities, 1978- (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - 07-100 Museum, 1979- (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - 07-100 Museum South Rotunda II, 1979- (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - 07-100 Dudley Herbarium, 1977- (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - 07-200 Chemistry, 1979- (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - 07-250 Organic Chemistry, 1979- (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - 07-260 Stauffer I, 1979- (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - 07-270 Stauffer II Physical Chemistry, 1979- (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - 07-280 Chemical Engineering Gazebo II, 1978- (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - 07-260,270,290 Stauffer I, II, II Fume Hoods, 1979- (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - 07-290 Stauffer III Chemical Engineering, 1979- (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - 07-300 Medical Center, 1979- (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - 07-300 Medical Center Ambulatory Care Facilities 1976 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - 07-300 Medical Center Cardio/Radio Expansion, 1978- (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - VII Educational Resources Building (Medical Center), 1974- (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - 07-300 Medical Center Immunology Building, 1975- (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - 07-300 Medical Center Materials Management, 1978- (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - 07-300 Medical Center Newborn Nursery, 1979- (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - 07-320 Cardiovascular Research Building, 1979- (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - 07- Cardiovascular Center, 1979- (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - 07-400 Falconer Library Biological Sciences, 1979- (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - 07-520/525 Sherman Fairchild Building and Auditorium, 1979- (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - 07-550 Louis B. Mayer Cance Biology Research Lab, 1977- (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - 07-900T Physical Therapy Building 1970- (Box 45, Folder 25)
  - 07-920T Psychiatry Clinic Building, 1974- (Box 45, Folder 26)
  - 07-940T Drug Interaction Temp. Building (SUMC), 1978- (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - 07-945T Stanford Hemodialysis Center, 1975- (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - 07-970T Koko's House, 1978- (Box 45, Folder 29)
  - 07-980T Orthopedic Research Module, 1978- (Box 45, Folder 30)
  - 08-100 Athletics and P.E., 1979- (Box 45, Folder 31)
  - 08-110 Daper Fieldhouse, 1979- (Box 45, Folder 32)
  - 08-200 Old Pavilion, 1979- (Box 45, Folder 33)
  - 08-300 Memorial Hall, 1979- (Box 45, Folder 34)
  - 08-300 Memorial Hall Advisory Group, 1979- (Box 45, Folder 35)
  - 08-350 Business Grad. School, 1979- (Box 45, Folder 36)
  - 08-350 "Pillars of Hercules III" Sculpture, 1979- (Box 45, Folder 37)
  - 08-350 Business School/Info. Project, 1971- (Box 45, Folder 38)
  - 08-400 Old Steam Plant (Band Quarters), 1979- (Box 45, Folder 39)
  - 08-400 ROTC/ARMORY 1972- (Box 45, Folder 40)
  - 08-400 Band Shack, 1974- (Box 45, Folder 41)
  - 08-500 Galvez House 200 Galvaz, 1979- (Box 45, Folder 42)
  - 08-600 Frost (Laurence) Amphitheatre, 1979- (Box 45, Folder 43)
  - 09-General Service Building, 1979- (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - 09-100 Plant Service Building, 1979- (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - 09-110 Stores--330 Bonair Siding, 1979- (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - 09-110 I.D. Mail, 1977- (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - 09-120 Credit Union, Stanford Federal, 1978- (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - 09-190 Telecommunications Center, 1978- (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - 09-190 Communications Modular Building (Breitrose), 1975- (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - 09-230 Fluoridation Station, 1977- (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - 09-250 Shell Service Station, 1975- (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - 09-300 Maples (Roscoe) Pavilion, 1979- (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - 09-310 Athletic Complex, 1979- (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - 09-400 Comisary/Food Service (Residence Halls), 1978- (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - 09- Centres Building (#546), 1975- (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - 09-500 Stadium, 1979- (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - 09-920T CCSC--Little Kid's Place, 1978- (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - 10-General, 1979- (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - 10-145 Escondido Village Highrise Mirrielees, 1979- (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - 10-170 Escondido Library--865 Escondido Road, 1979- (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - 10-180 Escondido Community Center--845 Escondido Road, 1977- (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - 10-300 Bing Nursery School, 1979- (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - 10-300 Bing Nursery School, 1978- (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - 10-310 Tower House--860 Escondido Road, 1979- (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - 10-320 Hacienda Apartments--860 Escondido Road, 1971- (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - 10-610 Alpha Sigma Phi--585 Cowell, 1976- (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - 10- Escondido Pool, 1975- (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - 11- Row House General, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - 11- Mayfield Avenue Recreational Facilities, 1975- (Box 46, Folder 27)
  - 11- CCSC Relocation, 1975- (Box 46, Folder 28)
  - 11-150 Stillman House, 1973- (Box 46, Folder 29)
  - 11-170 Old Stanford Elementary School, 1974- (Box 46, Folder 30)
  - 11-180 Grove I (Lasuen)--572 Mayfield, 1979- (Box 46, Folder 31)
  - 11-200 Grove II (Mayfield)--584 Mayfield, 1979- (Box 46, Folder 32)
  - 11-240 Jordan Co-op--620 Mayfield, 1978- (Box 46, Folder 33)
  - 11-260 Durand House--634 Mayfield, 1979- (Box 46, Folder 34)
  - 11-280 Roth House--813 Santa Ynez, 1978- (Box 46, Folder 35)
  - 11-300 Delta Tau Delta--650 San Juan, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 36)
  - 11-320 President's Residence--623 Mirada, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 37)
  - 11-330 Hanna (F.L. Wright) Residence thru Maintenance and Moving in Project, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 38)
  - 11-330 Hanna House, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 39)
  - 11-330 Hanna House 1975 (Box 46, Folder 40)
  - 11- Sub Committee on Faculty Staff Housing 1972 (Box 46, Folder 41)
  - 11-400 Ryan Laboratory, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 42)
  - 12-10 Golf Clubhouse, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - 12-30 Lathrop Gate House--200 Junipero Serra, 1979- (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - 12-50 Hansen Labs Storage, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - 12-70 Student Observatory I 1978 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - 12-70 Student Observatory II, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - 12-150 D.C. Power Building, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - 12-350 National Bureau Economic Research 1974 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - 12-400 Solar Observatory 1976 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - 13-40 Information Station (Palo Alto Drive) 1977 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - 14- SCIP & RLIN moves to Jordon Quad, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - 14-100 Central Steam & Chilled Water Plant 1978 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - 14-110 Ceder Hall 1977 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - 14-140 Redwood Hall 1977 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - 14-160 Polya Hall, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - 14-170 Pine Hall, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - 14- Netlofts 1967 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - 14- Vanderbilt Fish Collections 1971 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - 14-620 Bleeker Hall 1978 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - 14-610 Art Studios--Searsville Warehouse, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - 14-200 George Forsythe Hall, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - 14-200 George Forsythe Hall 1978 (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - 14-200 George Forsythe Hall 1977 (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - 14-200 Stanford Computer Facility, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - 14-900 Meyer-Buck Estate, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - 90-100 Hopkins Marine Station--Marinostat Building 1978 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - 90-100 Hopkins Marine Station Cannery, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - 90-100 Hopkins Marine Station--General 1975 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - 90-100 Hopkins Marine Station--General 1976 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - 90-100 Hopkins Marine Station--General, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - 90-100 Hopkins Marine Station--Facilities Evaluation Report 1976 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - 90-100 Hopkins Marine Station--Master Plan 1977 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - 90-110 Hopkins Marine Station--Loeb Laboratory 1978 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - 90-140 Hopkins Marine Station--Moterey Boat Works 1977 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - 90-909 800 Welsh Road--Rental (Blood Bank), 1979 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - 90-925 PI Meson Medical Center 1976 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - 90- Family Farm Road Flooding Re: Jasper Ridge 1970 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - 90- Fundraising Jasper Ridge 1975 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - 90- Hastorf Briefing Red: Jasper Ridge 1972 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - 90- Morrell Property Re: Jasper Ridge 1972 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - 90- Pinehill Subdivision (Frenchman's Hill) 1972 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - 90- Searsville Lake 1978 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - 90- Searsville Sailing 1977 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - 90- Shack riders 1972 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - 90- SLAC--Prep Project, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - 90- SLAC Synchotron, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - 90- Syntex Buildings 1971 (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - 90- Webb Ranch 1977 (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - Budget Files (85-080) (Box 48)
    - Fund Statement Summaries, 1977-78 (binder) (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Fund Statement Summaries, 1978-79 (binder) (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Fund Statement Summaries, 1979-80 (binder) (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Autumn Revisions, 1979 December; January 1980 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Budget Cycles, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Budget Forms, Instruction, 1974 thru 1978 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Budget Reduction Plan, 1974 thru 1976 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - General Correspondence--Budget Reductions, Short-falls, 1974-1979 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Guide for Budget Letters, 1973 thru 1977 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Protocols, 1973 thru 1980 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Budget Statements: Various Accounts (Box 49)
    - 1-RBE-101 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - 1-RBE-102 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - 1-RBF-212 (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - 1-RBF-223 (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - 1-RBF-629, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - 1-RBF-602., 1979 (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - 1-RBF-629, 1980 (Box 49, Folder 17)
    - 1-RBG--005 (Box 49, Folder 18)
    - 1-RBG-006 (Box 49, Folder 19)
    - 1-RBZ-007 (Box 49, Folder 20)
    - 1-RBZ-008 (Box 49, Folder 21)
    - 1-RBZ-035 (Box 49, Folder 22)
    - 1-RBZ-036 (Box 49, Folder 23)
    - 1-RBZ-042 (Box 49, Folder 24)
    - 1-RBZ-052 (Box 49, Folder 25)
    - 1-RBZ-062 (Box 49, Folder 26)
    - 1-RBZ-201 (Box 49, Folder 27)
    - 1-RBZ-202 (Box 49, Folder 28)
    - 1-RBZ-217 (Box 49, Folder 29)
    - 1-RBZ-218 (Box 49, Folder 30)
    - 1-RBZ-228 (Box 49, Folder 31)
    - 1-RBZ-231 (Box 49, Folder 32)
    - 1-RBZ-232 (Box 49, Folder 33)
    - 1-RBZ-233 (Box 49, Folder 34)
    - 1-RBZ-601 (Box 49, Folder 35)
    - 1-RBZ-602, 1980 (Box 49, Folder 36)
    - 1-RBZ-614 (Box 49, Folder 37)
    - 1-RBZ-615 (Box 49, Folder 38)
    - 1-RBZ-616 (Box 49, Folder 39)
    - 1-RBZ-617 (Box 49, Folder 40)
    - 1-RBZ-627 (Box 49, Folder 41)
    - 1-RBZ-656 (Box 49, Folder 42)
    - 1-RBZ-671 (Box 49, Folder 43)
    - 1-RBZ-681 (Box 49, Folder 44)
    - 1-RBZ-683 (Box 49, Folder 45)
    - 1-RBZ-686 (Box 49, Folder 46)
    - 2-RBG-211 (charged to 1-RBG-211 after 9/1/80) (Box 49, Folder 47)
    - 2-RBY-096 (Box 49, Folder 48)
    - 2-RBZ-603 (Box 49, Folder 49)
    - 2-RBZ-608 (Box 49, Folder 50)
    - 7-RBA-003 (Box 49, Folder 51)
    - 7-RBE-032 (Box 49, Folder 52)
    - 7-RBE-034 (Box 49, Folder 53)
    - 7-RBG-008 (Box 49, Folder 54)
    - 7-RBZ-001 (Box 49, Folder 55)
    - 7-RBZ-003 (Box 49, Folder 56)
    - 7-RBZ-004 (Box 49, Folder 57)
    - 7-RBZ-005 (Box 49, Folder 58)
    - 1-RBZ-006 (Box 49, Folder 59)
    - 7-RBZ-007 (Box 49, Folder 60)
    - 7-RBZ-008 (Box 49, Folder 61)
    - 7-RBZ-009 (Box 49, Folder 62)
    - 7-RBZ-010 (Box 49, Folder 63)
    - 7-RBZ-012 (Box 49, Folder 64)
    - 1-RBZ-013 (Box 49, Folder 65)
    - 7-RBZ-015 (Box 49, Folder 66)
    - 7-RBZ-016 (Box 49, Folder 67)
    - 7-RBZ-020 (Box 49, Folder 68)
    - 7-RBZ-028 (Box 49, Folder 69)
    - 7-RBZ-029 (Box 49, Folder 70)
    - 7-RBZ-042 (Box 49, Folder 71)
    - 7-RBZ-064 (Box 49, Folder 72)
    - 7-RBZ-093 (Box 49, Folder 73)
    - 7-RBZ-094 (Box 49, Folder 74)
    - 7-RBZ-095 (Box 49, Folder 75)
    - 7-RBZ-096 (Box 49, Folder 76)
    - 2-RBZ-601 (changed to 1-RBZ--605 9/1/80) (Box 49, Folder 77)
    - 2-RBZ-606 (Box 49, Folder 78)
    - 7-RBZ-096 (Box 49, Folder 79)
    - 7-RBZ-097 (Box 49, Folder 80)
    - 7-RBZ-098 (Box 49, Folder 81)
    - 7-RBZ-099 (Box 49, Folder 82)
    - 7-RBZ-603 (Box 49, Folder 83)
    - 7-RBZ-604 (Box 49, Folder 84)
    - 7-RCA-013 (Box 49, Folder 85)
    - 7-RDZ-001 (Box 49, Folder 86)
    - 7-RDZ-601 (Box 49, Folder 87)
    - 7-REA-065 (Box 49, Folder 88)
    - 8-RBZ-001 (Box 49, Folder 89)
    - 8-RBZ-601 (Box 49, Folder 90)
    - 8-RBZ-610 Joseph Drown Research Fund (1980-81 and earlier) Peat, Marwick, Mitchell, and Co. (Box 49, Folder 91)
    - Academic Planning Office, 1980-1981 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Admissions, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - ARLO, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Business and Finance, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - CRIS, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - DAPER, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Earth Sciences, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Education, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Development, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Dean of Student Affairs, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Dean of Student Affairs, Tresidder, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Engineering, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Financial Aids, Undergraduate, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Financial Aids, Graduate, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - Financial Aids, Graduate College Work Study (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - Graduate School of Business, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - Graduate Studies, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 17)
    - Honeycomb House (Hanna House), 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 18)
    - Hopkins Marine Station, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 19)
    - Hoover Institution, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 20)
    - Hospital, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 21)
    - Humanities and Sciences, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 22)
    - Humanities and Sciences Faculty Salaries Lists, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 23)
    - Independent Labs, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 24)
    - Law School,ABF, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 25)
    - Law School Faculty Planning, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 26)
    - Law School, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 27)
    - Law School, Metteer Will (Box 50, Folder 28)
    - Libraries, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 29)
    - LOTS, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 30)
    - Medicine, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 31)
    - Memorial Church, 1978079 (Box 50, Folder 32)
    - Overseas Studies, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 33)
    - Overseas Studies Current Transportation Policy (Box 50, Folder 34)
    - Overseas Studies Rome Classics Center (Box 50, Folder 35)
    - Overseas Studies Berlin Program, 1977-79 (Box 50, Folder 36)
    - President's/ Provost's Office, 1978-1979 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Press, 1978-1979 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Public Affairs, 1978-1979 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Registrar's Office, 1978-1979 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - SCIP, 1978-1979 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - SLAC, 1978-1979 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Summer Session, 1978-1979 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Undergraduate Studies, 1978-1979 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - University Counsel, 1978-1979 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - University Libraries, 1978-79--Equipment needs (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Values, Technology and Society Program, 1978-1979 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Values, Technology and Society Program, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Computer Costs Reallocation, 1976 (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - SCIP Background Material on Administrative Computing (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - SCIP Background Material on Administrative Computing (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - SCIP Background Material on Administrative Computing (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - SCIP Background Material on Administrative Computing (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - DOSA, Budget Protocol Letter, 1979-80 (Box 51, Folder 18)
- Budget Files, 1973-1981; Accession ARCH-1985-080
  - Fund statement summaries (binder), 1977-1978 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Fund statement summaries (binder), 1978-1979 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Fund statement summaries (binder), 1979-1980 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Autumn revisions, 1979 Dec-1980 Jan (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Budget cycles, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Budget Forms, instruction, 1974-1978 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Budget Reduction Plan, 1974-1976 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - General correspondence--budget reductions, shortfalls, 1974-1979 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Guide for budget letters, 1973-1977 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Protocols, 1973-1980 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Budget statements: various accounts, Undated
    The majority of files are undated. Exceptions are noted in the file listing.
    - 1-RBE-101 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - 1-RBE-102 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - 1-RBF-212 (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - 1-RBF-223 (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - 1-RBF-629, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - 1-RBF-602, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - I-RBF-629, 1980 (Box 49, Folder 17)
    - 1-RBG-005 (Box 49, Folder 18)
    - 1-RBG-006 (Box 49, Folder 19)
    - 1-RBZ-007 (Box 49, Folder 20)
    - 1-RBZ-008 (Box 49, Folder 21)
    - 1-RBZ-035 (Box 49, Folder 22)
    - 1-RBZ-036 (Box 49, Folder 23)
    - 1-RBZ-042 (Box 49, Folder 24)
    - 1-RBZ-052 (Box 49, Folder 25)
    - 1-RBZ-062 (Box 49, Folder 26)
    - 1-RBZ-201 (Box 49, Folder 27)
    - 1-RBZ-202 (Box 49, Folder 28)
    - 1-RBZ-217 (Box 49, Folder 29)
    - 1-RBZ-218 (Box 49, Folder 30)
    - 1-RBZ-228 (Box 49, Folder 31)
    - 1-RBZ-231 (Box 49, Folder 32)
    - 1-RBZ-232 (Box 49, Folder 33)
    - 1-RBZ-233 (Box 49, Folder 34)
    - 1-RBZ-601 (Box 49, Folder 35)
    - 1-RBZ-602, 1980 (Box 49, Folder 36)
    - 1-RBZ-614 (Box 49, Folder 37)
    - 1-RBZ-615 (Box 49, Folder 38)
    - 1-RBZ-616 (Box 49, Folder 39)
    - 1-RBZ-617 (Box 49, Folder 40)
    - 1-RBZ-627 (Box 49, Folder 41)
    - 1-RBZ-656 (Box 49, Folder 42)
    - 1-RBZ-671 (Box 49, Folder 43)
    - 1-RBZ-681 (Box 49, Folder 44)
    - 1-RBZ-683 (Box 49, Folder 45)
    - 1-RBZ-686 (Box 49, Folder 46)
    - 2-RBG-211 (changed to 1-RBG-211 after 9/1/80) (Box 49, Folder 47)
    - 2-RBY-096 (Box 49, Folder 48)
    - 2-RBZ-603 (Box 49, Folder 49)
    - 2-RBZ-608 (Box 49, Folder 50)
    - 7-RBA-003 (Box 49, Folder 51)
    - 7-RBE-032 (Box 49, Folder 52)
    - 7-RBE-034 (Box 49, Folder 53)
    - 7-RBG-008 (Box 49, Folder 54)
    - 7-RBZ-001 (Box 49, Folder 55)
    - 7-RBZ-003 (Box 49, Folder 56)
    - 7-RBZ-004 (Box 49, Folder 57)
    - 7-RBZ-005 (Box 49, Folder 58)
    - 7-RBZ-006 (Box 49, Folder 59)
    - 7-RBZ-007 (Box 49, Folder 60)
    - 7-RBZ-008 (Box 49, Folder 61)
    - 7-RBZ-009 (Box 49, Folder 62)
    - 7-RBZ-010 (Box 49, Folder 63)
    - 7-RBZ-012 (Box 49, Folder 64)
    - 7-RBZ-013 (Box 49, Folder 65)
    - 7-RBZ-015 (Box 49, Folder 66)
    - 7-RBZ-016 (Box 49, Folder 67)
    - 7-RBZ-020 (Box 49, Folder 68)
    - 7-RBZ-028 (Box 49, Folder 69)
    - 7-RBZ-029 (Box 49, Folder 70)
    - 7-RBZ-042 (Box 49, Folder 71)
    - 7-RBZ-064 (Box 49, Folder 72)
    - 7-RBZ-093 (Box 49, Folder 73)
    - 7-RBZ-094 (Box 49, Folder 74)
    - 7-RBZ-095 (Box 49, Folder 75)
    - 7-RBZ-096 (Box 49, Folder 76)
    - 2-RBZ-601 (changed to 1-RBZ-605 9/1/80) (Box 49, Folder 77)
    - 2-RBZ-606 (Box 49, Folder 78)
    - 7-RBZ-096 (Box 49, Folder 79)
    - 7-RBZ-098 (Box 49, Folder 81)
    - 7-RBZ-099 (Box 49, Folder 82)
    - 7-RBZ-603 (Box 49, Folder 83)
    - 7-RBZ-604 (Box 49, Folder 84)
    - 7-RCA-013 (Box 49, Folder 85)
    - 7-RDZ-001 (Box 49, Folder 86)
    - 7-RDZ-601 (Box 49, Folder 87)
    - 7-REA-065 (Box 49, Folder 88)
    - 8-RBZ-001 (Box 49, Folder 89)
    - 8-RBZ-601 (Box 49, Folder 90)
    - 8-RBZ-610 Joseph Drown Research Fund Peat, Marwick, Mitchel l, and Co., 1980-1981 and earlier (Box 49, Folder 91)
    - 7-RBZ-097 (Box 49, Folder 80)
  - Academic Planning Office, 1980-1981 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Admissions, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - ARLO, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Business and Finance, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - CRIS, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - DAPER, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Earth Sciences, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Education, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Development, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Dean of Student Affairs, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Dean of Student Affairs, Tresidder, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Engineering, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Financial Aids, Undergraduate, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Financial Aids, Graduate, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Financial Aids, graduate college work study, Undated (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Graduate School of Business, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Graduate Studies, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Honeycomb House (Hanna House), 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Hopkins Marine Station, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - Hoover Institution, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - Hospital, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - Humanities and Sciences, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - Humanities and Sciences faculty salaries lists, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 23)
  - Independent Labs, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 24)
  - Law School, ABF, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 25)
  - Law School faculty planning, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 26)
  - Law School, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 27)
  - Law School, Metteer Will, Undated (Box 50, Folder 28)
  - Libraries, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 29)
  - LOTS, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 30)
  - Medicine, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 31)
  - Memorial Church, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 32)
  - Overseas Studies, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 33)
  - Overseas Studies Current Transportation Policy, Undated (Box 50, Folder 34)
  - Overseas Studies Rome Classics Center, Undated (Box 50, Folder 35)
  - Overseas Studies Berlin Program, 1977-1979 (Box 50, Folder 36)
  - President's/Provost's Office, 1978-1979 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Press, 1978-1979 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Public Affairs, 1978-1979 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Registrar's Office, 1978-1979 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - SCIP, 1978-1979 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - SLAC, 1978-1979 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Summer Session, 1978-1979 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Undergraduate Studies, 1978-1979 (Box 51, Folder 8)